{
    "subject": "resource/Josh_Homme",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedMusicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Mastodon_(band)",
    "human_readable": "Josh Homme is associated with Mastodon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9411900639533997,
            "question": "What is Josh Homme's role in Mastodon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219819903373718,
            "question": "Besides Mastodon, what other bands has Josh Homme been involved with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9136472940444946,
            "question": "How long has Josh Homme been associated with Mastodon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7092333436012268,
            "question": "What band is Josh Homme associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636565625667572,
            "question": "Who is Josh Homme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46068647503852844,
            "question": "Is Josh Homme a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3256300985813141,
            "question": "Has Mastodon won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2902255654335022,
            "question": "What genre of music is Mastodon known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26634737849235535,
            "question": "Name a famous band fronted by Josh Homme."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.231416717171669,
            "question": "What are some of Mastodon's most popular songs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josh Homme is associated with Mastodon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7878_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous band fronted by Josh Homme.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7878_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Mastodon known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7878_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Mastodon won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7878_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7878_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information suggesting that Josh Homme is associated with the band Mastodon. Josh Homme is primarily described as a musician and singer for bands such as Queens of the Stone Age, Kyuss, and other projects, but there is no mention of his association with Mastodon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Mastodon\u2019s Brent Hinds interviews his friends Jesse Hughes and Dave Catching from Eagles Of Death Metal, but there is no indication that Josh Homme is involved with the interview or conversation.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention any association between Josh Homme and Mastodon. The only related information is a video featuring interviews with Jesse Hughes and Dave Catching from Eagles Of Death Metal by Brent Hinds from Mastodon, but this does not indicate an active or official association between Homme and Mastodon.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}